Guide to the JDub Records Archive 2001-2011 MSS.330
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Data Storage
  - Matisyahu - Marcelo Cabrera photos, 2005 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0049)
  - Matisyahu - Michael Sofronski photos, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0050)
  - Matisyahu - photos, 2004 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0051)
  - Matisyahu - Photos and video clips, Houston and Austin, TX, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0052)
  - Matisyahu - Pics, Seth Olenick, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0053)
  - Matisyahu - Pics, Seth Olenick, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0054)
  - Michael Priest Photography - Canal Room, 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0055)
  - Milk n Honey 4/28/09, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0056)
  - Milk n Honey - LA 4/28/09, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0057)
  - Milk n Honey - LA, Bar Lubitsch 6/16/09, 2009 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0058)
  - Nadav - "The Long Night" mixes, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0059)
  - New Israel Fun Benefit - Highline Ballroom Sept. 18, 2008 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0060)
  - Rooftop Roots 1, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0061)
  - Soulico - DVD Art, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0062)
  - Soulico - Pix, US Tour, March 2007 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0063)
  - Unity - pics, Undated (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0064)
  - Vodka Latka - Disc 1, 2006 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0065)
  - Vodka Latka - Disc 2, 2006 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0066)
  - Zachor - pics 12/02, 2002 (Box 21, Disk ID: 330.3.0067)
- Oversize Series II: Promotion and Events
  This series contains the oversize material from the Promotion and Events series.
  - Balkan Beat Box posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Balkan Beat Box poster, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "A Crazy Worldwide Hannukkah Party" poster board, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Girls in Trouble posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Golem posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Golem poster - signed and numbered, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - JDub 5th Anniversary poster - original, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - JDub Records banner (black and white), Undated (Roll-storage 1)
  - JDub Records banner (color), Undated (Roll-storage Shared Fales 098)
  - "Just for a Day" poster - signed, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Labor Day BBQ - poster original, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Matisyahu posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Matisyahu and Balkan Beat Box - poster original, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Matisyahu on Tour poster - signed, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Milk and Honey - Nextbook Inc., Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Mixed artist posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Mixed holiday / festival posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Pardes - Memorial Concert poster - signed, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - So Called posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Soulico posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sway Machinery posters, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)